{
    "target_configs": {
        "player": {
            "name": [
                "player_10_0IFLTY",
                "player_5_0IFLTY",
                "player_15_0IFLTY"
            ],
            "app_id": [
                10,
                5,
                15
            ],
            "animation": [
                "pick_up",
                "crouch",
                "liedown"
            ],
            "feature_caption": [
                "A man with medium skin, wearing sunglasses, maroon polo shirt, beige pants, brown shoes, and a watch",
                "A female soldier wearing green tactical uniform, backpack, and black boots. Hair is tied back. She carries a utility vest and accessories.",
                "A bald man with medium skin, wearing a brown turtleneck, dark pants, and brown shoes."
            ],
            "start_pos": [
                [
                    812.392,
                    8981.09,
                    1248.275,
                    0.0,
                    -90.0,
                    0.0
                ],
                [
                    815.973,
                    9093.641,
                    1248.15,
                    0,
                    118.08268077990186,
                    0
                ],
                [
                    945.626,
                    8980.806,
                    1248.15,
                    0,
                    -97.36853933757607,
                    0
                ]
            ],
            "type": [
                "None",
                "None",
                "None"
            ]
        }
    },
    "sample_configs": {
        "sample_center": [
            899.728,
            9590.439,
            1248.15
        ],
        "sample_radius": 815.575974756163
    },
    "refer_agents_category": [
        "player"
    ],
    "safe_start": [
        [
            1444.541,
            8741.05,
            1277.023,
            0,
            154.68369383322448,
            0
        ],
        [
            642.447,
            9281.684,
            1248.15,
            0,
            -50.68090736417221,
            0
        ],
        [
            842.818,
            9585.641,
            1248.15,
            0,
            -88.46686455743998,
            0
        ]
    ],
    "Questions": {
        "relative_distance": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_woman_in_camo_vest, the_man_in_burgundy_polo_and_light_pants or the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants?",
                "options": [
                    "A. The_man_in_burgundy_polo_and_light_pants",
                    "B. The_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants"
                ],
                "answer": "A. The_man_in_burgundy_polo_and_light_pants"
            }
        },
        "counting": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "How many people are present in the scene?",
                "answer": "three"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "How many humans are in a crouch position?",
                "answer": "one"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "How many individuals are lying down?",
                "answer": "one"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "How many men are in the scene?",
                "answer": "two"
            },
            "Question 5": {
                "question": "How many individuals in the scene are not bald?",
                "answer": "two"
            },
            "Question 6": {
                "question": "How many people in the scene are not wearing glasses?",
                "answer": "two"
            }
        },
        "state": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "What's the state of the woman in the camo vest?",
                "options": [
                    "A. standing",
                    "B. running",
                    "C. crouch",
                    "D. jumping"
                ],
                "answer": "C. crouch"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "What's the state of the bald man in the brown sweater and black pants?",
                "options": [
                    "A. standing",
                    "B. liedown",
                    "C. sitting",
                    "D. walking"
                ],
                "answer": "B. liedown"
            }
        },
        "relative_location": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "Where is the woman in camo vest relative to the man in burgundy polo and light pants?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the front of",
                    "B. To the left of",
                    "C. Behind",
                    "D. Above"
                ],
                "answer": "B. To the left of"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "Where is the bald man in brown sweater and black pants relative to the man in burgundy polo and light pants?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the left of",
                    "B. To the right of",
                    "C. In front of",
                    "D. Behind"
                ],
                "answer": "C. In front of"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "Where is the man in burgundy polo and light pants relative to the woman in camo vest?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the right of",
                    "B. To the left of",
                    "C. In front of",
                    "D. Behind"
                ],
                "answer": "B. To the left of"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "Where is the bald man in brown sweater and black pants relative to the woman in camo vest?",
                "options": [
                    "A. Behind",
                    "B. To the right of",
                    "C. In front-left of",
                    "D. Above"
                ],
                "answer": "C. In front-left of"
            }
        }
    }
}